http://www.mpgroup.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyWe recognize that you may be concerned about our use and disclosure of your personal information. Your privacy is very important to us, and the following will inform you of the information that we, MPGroup, may collect from you, and how it is used. By using our website, www.mpgroup.com, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.Information CollectionWe may collect non-personal information, such as a domain name and IP Address. The domain name and IP address reveals nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We may also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, what brought you to our Website, as well as which of our Web pages you have accessed.Additionally, if you communicate with us regarding our Website or our services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Information UseWe use the collected information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our services and Website, fulfilling requests for information, and providing customer support.SecurityWe follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.If we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesWe use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.SharingWe will not sell or otherwise provide the information we collect to outside third parties for the purpose of direct or indirect mass email marketing.We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on our companyProtect and defend the rights or property of our Website and related propertiesIdentify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing our Website or its related propertiesPlease keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion boards, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.LinksThis Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.ConsentBy using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of information as specified above. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. Please review this page frequently to remain up-to-date with the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at
(800) 684-9100 or via mail Attn: Privacy Officer, 1202 Greenacre Avenue, West Hollywood, CA 90046-5708.
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for MPGroup relating
to mpgroup.scorpiontechnology.com. This privacy notice applies solely
to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through
the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the Information Collection, Use,
and Sharing.
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only
have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email
or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information
to anyone. ALL INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THIS SITE AND SUBSEQUENTLY BY
ANY OTHER MEANS SHALL BE CONSIDERED STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you
contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party
outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to
tell you about information of potential interest specials, new products
or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do
the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone
number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive
information via the website, your information is protected both online
and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that
information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can
verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web
browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address
of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online,
we also protect your information offline. The computers/servers in which
we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored
on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our
site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use
a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more
than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable
us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience
on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable
information on our site.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are
not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read
the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable
information.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should
contact us immediately via telephone at (323) 874-8973 or via mail Attn:
Privacy Policy, 1202 Greenacre Avenue, West Hollywood, CA 90046-5708.
Unique Among Construction Experts
Founder of MPGroup, Michael S. Poles is a construction consultant and expert
witness with 54 years of hands-on construction experience and is a mediator
trained at the Pepperdine University School of Law. Mr. Poles is committed
to the highest professional and ethical standards to help lawyers and
their clients realize positive results. Michael leads our team of experts,
offering comprehensive and personalized services to meet your varied and
specific needs.
Hear More about Us
Learn more about Mr. Poles [+]
Schedule Your
Initial Consultation
The purpose of the initial telephone consultation is for the expert and
the lawyer to evaluate whether the expert candidate is sufficiently qualified
to testify on the issues of the case at hand. There is ordinarily no charge
for an initial telephone consultation with our office, as 30 minutes is
customarily allotted without any charge.
Should you wish to discuss the substantive issues of your case in detail,
whereby we are “working the case” beyond 30 minutes and providing technical, discovery and strategic
advice, the consultation is subject to an hourly charge payable via credit
card. You may also retain our services via credit card, and thereby formally
designate our expert(s) to the court.
In furtherance of retainer, telephone consultation(s), photograph and/or
document review, please call our office to discuss the case issues and
how much time you wish to purchase. Fifteen (15) minute increments will apply.
We utilize 50 plus years of hands-on experience and construction technical expertise
We have experience with many businesses, insurance companies, law firms,
and individual attorneys
We have served clients located throughout the United States and particularly
within California
We are specialists with California building codes and construction law
We offer a highly specialized and experienced team of professionals ready
to meet your goals
We provide construction litigation support and mediation services that
get positive results for our clients
We are a collaboration of senior professionals and veterans of the United
States Military committed to the highest professional and ethical standards
We are experienced with most construction issues ranging from
SAFETY to
CONSTRUCTION DEFECTS
Name
Please enter your name.
Email
This isn't a valid email address.
Please enter your email address.
Phone
This isn't a valid phone number.
Please enter your phone number.
Firm Name
Address
Please enter your address.
City
Please enter your city.
State
Select State
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaInternationalIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWashington, DCWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingGuam
Please select a state.
Zip
Please enter your zip code.
How did you find us?
Court Location
Trial Date
Court Case Number
Case Caption
Are you a Attorney/Consumer?
I am an Attorney
I am a Consumer
I'm neither
Please select an option.
Message
Please enter a message.
Send Information
